Hilda Mason, Board of Education 136
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - California/Connecticut/Colorado (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Budget Articles, 1976 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Washington D.C Teacher, 1967 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - A Primer for Parent and Community involvment in the Public School System of D.C., 1979 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - A Quest for Equal Education Opportunity in a Major Urban School District, 1975 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings: Symposium on Increasing Minority Participation in Engineering, 1973 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins, 1975-1977 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Signal: Washington State School Directors Association, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Board Censures Shaffer-Corona, 1980 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - ASBD Bulletin, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Language in Education: Problems and Prospects in Research and Training, 1975 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Arizona School Board Assn. Report Card, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - The Bicentennial America's Challenge to Fulfill Dr. King's Dream, Undated (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Arizona School Board Association, 1974-1976 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - School Cost Center Reporting Resolution, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - School Cost Center Reporting Resolution, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - The National Urban Coalition, 1978 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Public Hearing on Bill 2-3 "Educational Accountablity Act of, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - Discover D.C: A Competency Based Curriculum Secondary Teacher's Manual ( 1 of 2), 1977 (Box 169, Folder 15)
  - Discover D.C: A Competency Based Curriculum Secondary Teacher's Manual ( 2 of 2), 1977 (Box 169, Folder 16)
  - Public Schools of DC - Title I Comprehensive Program, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 17)
  - International Trade and Convention Center and Recommendations on How to Generate Additional Income to St. Mary's County During Next Five Years, Undated (Box 169, Folder 18)
  - Georgetown U. Law Ctr., Undated (Box 169, Folder 19)
  - Gilbert Ben W. School Census, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 20)
  - Freedom of Speech - Press - 1976 (Box 169, Folder 21)
  - Gordon and 4 Yr. High School, 1976-1981 (Box 169, Folder 22)
  - ID/Identification Cards, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 23)
  - Mission of Common Concerns, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 24)
  - Morgan Community School Proposals etc., 1968-1973 (Box 169, Folder 25)
  - The President's Annual Report - 1975, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 26)
  - Nelsen Commission Report, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 27)
  - Parenting, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 28)
  - Parking, 1973 (Box 169, Folder 29)
  - Right to Read, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 30)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1974-1975 (1 of 3) (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1974-1975 (2 of 3) (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1974-1975 (3 of 3) (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1973-1974 (1 of 3) (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1973-1974 (2 of 3) (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1973-1974 (3 of 3) (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1975-1976 (1 of 2) (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1975-1976 (2 of 2) (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1973-1974 (1 of 2) (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Systematic Educational Program Assessment: School Year 1973-1974 (2 of 2) (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Public Information Kit - Washington Technical Institute, 1971 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Teachers, 1965-1967 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Ashpet, Undated (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Introduction to the Imagination Activities for Creative Writing, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Black Women's Community Development Foundation Correspondence, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Julius Hobson, 1970 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Alice Deal Junior High School Home and School Association Newsletter, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - Hendley Community School Council Scholarship Ball, Undated (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Challenge - A Quarterly Publication, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Agenda for the Community Meeting of the Board of Education, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - Eastern High School Dance Group, 1973 (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - Black Repertory Company Correspondence, Undated (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Howland H. Mason Correspondence, 1971 (Box 172, Folder 15)
  - MLK Library Dedication Week, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 16)
  - Ground Breaking Ceremony for the New Washington Technical Institute Campus, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 17)
  - LaFayette Elementary School, Undated (Box 172, Folder 18)
  - Timely Teaching Tips Department of Supervision and Instruction, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 19)
  - City Wide Activities Semester I - 1971-72, Undated (Box 172, Folder 20)
  - Supplement Afro-American History, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 21)
  - Personnel Items Approved by the Committee of the Whole Concerning Personnel, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 22)
  - Kindergarten Correspondence Mini-Course December Kindergarten Suggestions, Undated (Box 172, Folder 23)
  - Elementary Supervision and Instruction, Undated (Box 172, Folder 24)
  - Oberkirchen Children's Choir, Undated (Box 172, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Citizens for Better Public Education Correspondence, 1967 (Box 172, Folder 26)
  - In House New Items, 1967 (Box 172, Folder 27)
  - Libraries A Go-Go Vol. 2 No. 2, 1967 (Box 172, Folder 28)
  - Agenda for Board of Education, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 29)
  - DCEA Protests Shaw Attacks, Undated (Box 172, Folder 30)
  - New Paperbacks in the Library, Undated (Box 172, Folder 31)
  - The Community Development Process, Undated (Box 172, Folder 32)
  - Washington Teachers' Union Correspondence, 1967 (Box 172, Folder 33)
  - Meet Kathy McGregor, Undated (Box 172, Folder 34)
  - DC Congress of Parents and Teachers, Undated (Box 172, Folder 35)
  - Questionnaire, Undated (Box 172, Folder 36)
  - Misc. Correspondence and Speeches, 1973 (Box 172, Folder 37)
  - The Cromwell Academy, 1973 (Box 172, Folder 38)
  - Teacher Transfer Request Form, 1973 (Box 172, Folder 39)
  - Sex Education, Undated (Box 172, Folder 40)
  - City Wide Activities, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 41)
  - Resume, Undated (Box 172, Folder 42)
  - Positions Division of Adult and Continuing Education, Undated (Box 172, Folder 43)
  - The AFT Way Collective Bargaining Works, Undated (Box 172, Folder 44)
  - Grants for Research in Education, 1973 (Box 172, Folder 45)
  - Manpower Directions in Metropolitan Washington D.C, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 46)
  - Program Announcement, 1974 (Box 172, Folder 47)
  - Other Instructional and Support Programs, 1977 (Box 172, Folder 48)
  - DC - 1974-1979 Capital Improvements Program, 1973 (Box 172, Folder 49)
  - The Psycho Analytical Study of the Child Vols. 1-25, 1972 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Career Education in the Inner City Interdisciplinary Curriculum Grades 1-6, 1976 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Evaluation Career Opportunities Program, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - The Franklin School Building, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Parent Involvment in Compensatory Education Programs, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Public Schools of the Distric of Columbia Federal Grant Supplement, 1972 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - D.C Public Schools Justifications for the 1974 Budget, 1972 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - D.C Public Schools Justifications for the 1974 Budget, 1972 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Approved Budgets for the School and Fiscal Year ending June 30 1977, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - School Board's Advertised Budgets for the Scohol and Fiscal Year Ending June 30 1977, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Applications for Federal Assistance, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - The Metropolitan Area Boards of Education Basic Information Guide, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Teacher's Manual for the Career Development Curriculum Guides 7th and 8th Grades, Undated (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Curriculum Guide: Public Schools of the District of Columbia, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Curriculum Guide, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Marine Science Program at Randall High School, 1977 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Trinity College Women's Meeting, 1977 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - National Black Women's Political Leadership Caucus, 1977 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - Career Development Exemplary Project, 1968 (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - Amended Annual Program Plan FY 1976 (Box 174, Folder 14)
  - State Plan - Adult Ed, 1976-1977 (Box 174, Folder 15)
  - Office Copies, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 16)
  - DC - 1975-1980 Capital Improvement Program, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - Board of Education the FY 1973 Operating Budget, 1972 (Box 174, Folder 18)
  - Justifications for the 1973 Budget for DC, 1972 (Box 174, Folder 19)
  - Northeast Cities Conference December 1976 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Synergist - Special High School Issue, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting Reports and Delegate Manual Massachusetts Association of School Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Northeast Cities Conference December 1970, 1976 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Excerises, 1972 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - The Boardman, 1974-1975 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation of the Right to Reap State Planning Program of the Public Schools of DC - 1975-1976 Final Report (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - The Dolphine - 1972 C Melvin Sharpe Health School (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - 1974 School Board News Bulletin (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - 67 Demands School Boards Make, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Atlanta Inquirer, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - ISAB Update, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Week in Review, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - KSBA School Board Reporter, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - The Energy the Faith - A Thanksgiving Tribute, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Success Stories from Illinois, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Illinois Task Force on Declining Enrollment, Undated (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - ISBA Journal ( 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - ISBA Journal ( 2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - Headlines, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Information Legislative Service, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - Spring Meeting of Northeast Region of N.S.B.A March 12-14, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - Board- O- Gram, 1976 (Box 176, Folder 16)
  - RIASC Newsletter, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 17)
  - School Boards Association Bulletin, 1975 (Box 176, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education ASBSD Bulletin, 1974-1977 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - PSBA Bulletin, 1974 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Focus on Detroit Region One, Undated (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Michigan School Board Journal, 1974-1976 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - VSBA Newsletter (1 of 2), 1974-1977 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - VSBA Newsletter (2 of 2), 1974-1977 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Labor Relations Bulletin and 38th VSSDA Annual Meeting Program, 1974-1977 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Signal Newsletter, 1975 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Arlington Public Schools Correspondence, 1976 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - The Technique - 1976 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - VSBA Newsletter - 1977 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Alexandria City Public Schools The Alexandria Plan Part II, 1975 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - 1972 Vermont State Aid (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Standards of Quality and Objectives for Public Schools in Virginia 1974-1976, Undated (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Signal, 1976-1977 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Volunteer School Backed, 1974 (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - Wisconsin News, 1977 (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - Compass, 1974-1975 (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - Wisconsin School News, 1974-1976 (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - WSSDA Signal, 1974-1976 (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - Handbook of Management Standards for Awarding High School Diplomas, 1975 (Box 178, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts, 1976 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - MSMA Bulletin - A School Management Bulletin, 1975 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - MASC Journal, 1974-1976 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - MASC Bulletin - Boston Massachusetts, 1974-1977 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - So You Want to be A School Board Member?, 1975 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Mid Atlantic Community Education Consortium, 1975-1976 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - The Overseas Schools Newspaper January - February 1976 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Decentralization, 1974 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - For Your Child, Undated (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Annual Program Plan, 1977 (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Contact - Magazine of Black Involvement, 1971 (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - Children of Cardozo - Tell It Like it Is, 1968 (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - Untangling - Vietnam Discussion Materials for Boys and Girls, Undated (Box 179, Folder 13)
  - Education in America, 1971 (Box 179, Folder 14)
  - A WTOP Editorial, 1971 (Box 179, Folder 15)
  - Abraham Lincoln Junior High School Model School Division, 1968 (Box 179, Folder 16)
  - Today's Changing Roles: An Approach to Non Sexist Teaching, 1974 (Box 179, Folder 17)
  - Press Release - 1971 (Box 179, Folder 18)
  - DC Science Fair Association Correspondence, 1977 (Box 179, Folder 19)
  - DC Youth Orchestra, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 20)
  - School Board Candidate Endorsement Poll- Important, Undated (Box 179, Folder 21)
  - Federal Register - Department of Health Educatoin and Welfare, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 22)
  - Summary of Legislation Introduced or Co-sponsored by Hilda Mason, 1978 (Box 179, Folder 23)
  - William Coxe - Director Division of Building and Grounds Memo, 1977 (Box 179, Folder 24)
  - Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 179, Folder 25)
  - Summary of Legislation Introduced or Co-sponsored by Hilda Mason - 1978 (Box 179, Folder 26)
  - For Better Education Inc., 1984 (Box 179, Folder 27)
  - Fire Prevention Try n Find, Undated (Box 179, Folder 28)
  - Advisory and Learning Exchange, 1981 (Box 179, Folder 29)
  - Encore! - Washington Post, 1981 (Box 179, Folder 30)
  - Roof Corresponding, 1977 (Box 179, Folder 31)
  - Get Online with a Future Center Class, Undated (Box 179, Folder 32)
  - Public Education in Downtown D.C, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 33)
  - Distract Education, 1983 (Box 179, Folder 34)
  - We Salute Dwight S. Cropp, 1978 (Box 179, Folder 35)
  - Fifeieth Anniversary Auction Invitation, 1983 (Box 179, Folder 36)
  - Latin American Film Project, Undated (Box 179, Folder 37)
  - Takoma Community School - PTA Newsletter, 1977 (Box 179, Folder 38)
  - City Wide Learning City, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 39)
  - Committee of the Whole Concerning Personnel, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 40)
  - Ward IV Meeting 10/25/72, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 41)
  - Agenda for Board of Education Meeting on November 15, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 42)
  - Agenda - November 15 1972 (Box 179, Folder 43)
  - Head Table Guests, Undated (Box 179, Folder 44)
  - Garnet - Patterson, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 45)
  - Everybody Fits in, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 46)
  - Committee of the Whole Concerning Personnel Monday - October 16 1972 (Box 179, Folder 47)
  - Committee of the Whole Personnel November 13 1972 (Box 179, Folder 48)
  - Superintendent Docket for Meeting of Committee of the Whole Concerning Personnel 11/13/1972 (Box 179, Folder 49)
  - Liquor License Applications, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 50)
  - Veterans Education - Course Approvals and Reinvestigation of Institutions, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 51)
  - The Rabaut Rambler - 1972-1973 (Box 179, Folder 52)
  - Let's Get Involved, Undated (Box 179, Folder 53)
  - Priorities for HWC Fudning of Huamn Serviceds, 1973 (Box 179, Folder 54)
  - Pogo Primer for Parents (TV Division), 1963 (Box 179, Folder 55)
  - Negro Americans - the Weekly Newsmagazine, 1964 (Box 179, Folder 56)
  - Martin Luther King Memorial Library A Living Resource, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 57)
  - Counselor - Professional, 1966-1967 (Box 179, Folder 58)
  - Opportunities in Vista - A Fact Booklet, 1967 (Box 179, Folder 59)
  - Bell Ringers Correspondence, 1967 (Box 179, Folder 60)
  - Counselor's Check up List, Undated (Box 179, Folder 61)
  - Join Now: Support your Bargaining Agent Application, Undated (Box 179, Folder 62)
  - Georgetown Day School, Undated (Box 179, Folder 63)
  - Washington Teachers Union Correspondence, 1967 (Box 179, Folder 64)
  - Handwritten notes, Undated (Box 179, Folder 65)
  - Books about Negro Life for Children, 1963 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Washington Teacher's Union Spotlight the Teachers' Voice, 1967 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Time - The Weekly New Magazine March 3 1967 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Petition on Student Discipline, Undated (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Washington Teachers Union Opinion Survey No. 1, 1967 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - DC Education Association Newsletter, 1967 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Danna A. Bell - Russel Email, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - School Aid Distributed Children Washington Post - 1967 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - AFT/Washington Teachers' Union Pamphlet, Undated (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Address to the D.C Teachers Union, 1965 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - The Unexpected Minority: White Children In an Urban Classroom, 1974 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Lawrence Johnson and Associates Inc. Corporate Capabailty Statement, 1976 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - National for Black Child Development, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 14)
  - Danzanksy Asks Suburbs Aid in Achieving DC Home Rule, Undated (Box 180, Folder 15)
  - Make Education Top Priority, 1973 (Box 180, Folder 16)
  - Gordon High Students Lauded as "Enviornmentalists of the Year", 1973 (Box 180, Folder 17)
  - External Agency List, 1973 (Box 180, Folder 18)
  - High School Equivalent Certification, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 19)
  - Tuition Exemptions, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 20)
  - Superintendent Docket, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 21)
  - Recommendation for Filling the Position of Assistant Principal Special Education Center, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 22)
  - Lawrence F. Briscoe Resume, Undated (Box 180, Folder 23)
  - Application Materials/Resume, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 24)
  - Washington Post Academy Program, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 25)
  - Budget Digest of Departmental Requests for Fiscal, 1961 (Box 180, Folder 26)
  - Budget Digest of Developmental Requests for Fiscal Year 1963, 1961 (Box 180, Folder 27)
  - Journey in Discovery - The Thirteen College Curriculum Program, 1969 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - A Needed Dimension in Public School Labor Negotiations, Undated (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Unions Recognized by D.CD Board of Education, Undated (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Estimated Average Annual Slaraies of Teachers During 1976-1977, Undated (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Teacher Salary Analysis, Undated (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Excerpt - Agreement Between the Board of Education of DC and Washington Teachers' Union, 1976-1978 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Office of Education, Undated (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Local School Advisory Committees, Undated (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - The Brent Journal, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Folder List, Undated (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Public Private School Exchange is in Jeapordy, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Woman Today, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 12)
  - Meeting of Committee on Adminstrative Services, 1974 (Box 181, Folder 13)
  - Dwight Cropp Memo, 1974 (Box 181, Folder 14)
  - Mrs. Virginia Morris Memo, 1975 (Box 181, Folder 15)
  - Citizens Advisory Council to the Superintendent first Meeting Memo, 1975 (Box 181, Folder 16)
  - The Urban Superintendency on the Brink, Undated (Box 181, Folder 17)
  - Council of D.C - D.C Law 2-1 Additional Teachers' Salary Act Amendments of, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 18)
  - Hilda Mason on Pay Raises for Police Officers/Firefighters/Teachers/School Officers, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 19)
  - Washington Parents' Union, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 20)
  - Geyelin Correspondence, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 21)
  - School Calendar Vacations and Holidays Statement of Hilda Rowland M. Mason, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 22)
  - Elington Visual Arts Faculty, Undated (Box 181, Folder 23)
  - Rifted Teachers are Reinstated, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 24)
  - Newsletter - Ward Tour Council on Education, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 25)
  - The Women's International Religious Fellowship Program "Our City - A World Community", 1975 (Box 181, Folder 26)
  - Resolutions Adopted by Delegates to the National Women's Conference Nov. 18-21 1977 (Box 181, Folder 27)
  - Messages from Black Women, Undated (Box 181, Folder 28)
  - Ambrosia Shepherd Correspondence, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 29)
  - Statement Taken By Parents at Press Conference at Hawthorne School Jan. 9 1978 (Box 181, Folder 30)
  - Organized Citizenery Correspondence, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 31)
  - City Observance for MLK - 1978 (Box 181, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Review - 1978 (Box 181, Folder 33)
  - Non-Personnel Allocation Memo, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 34)
  - La Concha - the Oyster Shell, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 35)
  - William H. Rumsey Correspondence, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 36)
  - Report: Meeting of the Board of Education Members Superintendent of Schools - Dr. Vincent E. Reed, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 37)
  - Home Business Visits by Police Cut Crime in One Area by 86 Pct, Undated (Box 181, Folder 38)
  - Ellen Metter Email, 1994 (Box 181, Folder 39)
  - Vincent Reed Correspondence Regarding Oyster School, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 40)
  - Annual Budget Correspondence, 1977 (Box 181, Folder 41)
  - A Needed Dimension in Public School Labor Negotiations, Undated (Box 181, Folder 42)
  - Symposium '78 Teaching Relationsihps, 1978 (Box 181, Folder 43)
  - Federal Programs Monitoring Process Project Audit, 1973 (Box 181, Folder 44)
  - Procedures for Submission of Proposals Related to Education of Handicapped Children and Youth in DC - 1973-1974, 1972 (Box 181, Folder 45)
  - List of Exhibitors, Undated (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Associates for Renewal in Education, Undated (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - WTU - 1984 Scholarship Benefit Ball (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - WTU - 1984 Scholarship Benefit Ball (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Equalization Report, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - City Council Legislation - Recall of Elected Officials, 1975 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Public Hearing on the Status of Board of Education and the Organization and Administration of DC Public Schools, 1975 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - City Council FY 1976 Questions/Education/Recreation and Youth Affairs Committee, 1975 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Series List, Undated (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Big School Board Gets Even Bigger, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Statement of Hilda Rowland M. Mason FY 1977 Budget Estimates, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - National School Names, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 12)
  - Mayor Among Others Receives Award, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - Starr King Graduates Newsletter, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 14)
  - Misc. News Article, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 15)
  - DC Community Archive Collection Info, Undated (Box 182, Folder 16)
  - Public Education in Downtown D.C, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 17)
  - The 66th Annual Convention DC Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 18)
  - Ward 2 Round Table Talks on Our Public Schools, Undated (Box 182, Folder 19)
  - Thank you note from Russell and Mabel, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 20)
  - Board of Education News, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 21)
  - Ambassador of the People's Republic of Bulgaria, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 22)
  - Interim Evaluation Report, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 23)
  - Email Threads, 1994 (Box 182, Folder 24)
  - Paul Robeson Friendship Society Salutes the People of the Soviet Union, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 25)
  - School Demographic, Undated (Box 182, Folder 26)
  - Ross School Newsletter, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 27)
  - National Survey of School Board Members, Undated (Box 182, Folder 28)